Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Subject File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 90-217)
  - Domestic programs
    - Defense
      - Press releases
        - 1974 May-June (Box-folder 115: 15-16)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 115: 17-18)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 115: 19)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 115: 20)
          - April (Box-folder 115: 21)
        - 1973 April (Box-folder 115: 22)
        - 1974 March-April (Box-folder 115: 23-24)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 115: 25)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 115: 26)
        - 1970
          - July (Box-folder 115: 27)
          - November-December (Box-folder 115: 28-29)
        - 1971 December (Box-folder 115: 30)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 115: 31)
          - July-October (Box-folder 115: 32-35)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 115: 36-37)
      - Reports
        - 1972 February (Box-folder 115: 38)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 115: 39)
      - Schedules
        - 1969 June (Box-folder 115: 40)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 115: 41)
          - July (Box-folder 115: 42)
        - 1974 June (Box-folder 115: 43)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 115: 44)
        - 1969
          - March (Box-folder 115: 45)
          - December (Box-folder 115: 46)
        - 1970
          - January (Box-folder 115: 47)
          - December (Box-folder 115: 48)
        - 1971
          - February-March (Box-folder 115: 49-50)
          - October-November (Box-folder 115: 51-52)
        - 1972
          - August-September (Box-folder 115: 53-54)
          - November (Box-folder 115: 55)
        - 1973
          - September (Box-folder 115: 56)
          - November (Box-folder 115: 57)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 115: 58)
      - Telegrams
        - Undated (Box-folder 116: 1)
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 116: 2)
        - 1971 February-March (Box-folder 116: 3-4)
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 116: 5)
      - Television news reports
        - 1971 February (Box-folder 116: 6)
        - 1974 February-July (Box-folder 116: 7-12)
    - District of Columbia home rule
      - Fact sheets, 1971 April (Box-folder 116: 13)
      - General (Box-folder 116: 14)
      - Meetings, 1972 April (Box-folder 116: 15)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 116: 16)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 116: 17)
          - November (Box-folder 116: 18)
      - Messages
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 116: 19)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 116: 20)
      - Press briefings
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 116: 21)
        - 1971
          - January (Box-folder 116: 22)
          - September (Box-folder 116: 23)
        - 1972
          - May (Box-folder 116: 24)
          - December (Box-folder 116: 25)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 116: 26)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 116: 27)
      - Press conferences
        - 1970 August (Box-folder 116: 28)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 116: 29)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 116: 30)
      - Press releases, 1970 May (Box-folder 116: 31)
      - Printed matter, 1971 April (Box-folder 116: 32)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 116: 33)
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 116: 34)
        - 1972 April (Box-folder 116: 35)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 116: 36)
        - 1969 April (Box-folder 116: 37)
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 116: 38)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 116: 39)
    - Drugs
      - Correspondence, 1971
        - July (Box-folder 116: 40)
        - October (Box-folder 116: 41)
      - Executive orders
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 116: 42)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 116: 43)
          - July (Box-folder 116: 44)
      - Fact sheets
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 116: 45)
        - 1971
          - General (Box-folder 116: 46)
          - March (Box-folder 116: 47)
          - June (Box-folder 116: 48)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 116: 49)
          - March (Box-folder 116: 50)
          - April (Box-folder 116: 51)
          - July (Box-folder 116: 52)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 116: 53)
          - September (Box-folder 116: 54)
          - November (Box-folder 116: 55)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 116: 56)
          - May (Box-folder 116: 57)
      - General (Box-folder 116: 58)
      - Meetings
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 116: 59)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 116: 60)
          - June-July (Box-folder 116: 61-62)
          - September (Box-folder 116: 63)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 116: 64)
          - July (Box-folder 116: 65)
          - September-October (Box-folder 116: 66-67)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 116: 68)
          - November (Box-folder 116: 69)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 116: 70)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 116: 71)
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 116: 72)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 116: 73)
          - June-July (Box-folder 116: 74-75)
          - September (Box-folder 116: 76)
        - 1972
          - March-April (Box-folder 116: 77-78)
          - July (Box-folder 116: 79)
          - December (Box-folder 116: 80)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 116: 81)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 116: 82)
      - Messages
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 117: 1)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 117: 2)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 117: 3)
      - News summaries, 1971 July (Box-folder 117: 4)
      - Pool reports
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 117: 5)
        - 1972 July (Box-folder 117: 6)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 117: 7)
        - 1971
          - May-June (Box-folder 117: 8-9)
          - September (Box-folder 117: 10)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 117: 11)
        - 1973 July (Box-folder 117: 12)
        - 1974
          - May (Box-folder 117: 13)
          - November (Box-folder 117: 14)
      - Press conferences
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 117: 15)
        - 1971
          - May-June (Box-folder 117: 16-17)
          - September (Box-folder 117: 18)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 117: 19)
          - July (Box-folder 117: 20)
          - September (Box-folder 117: 21)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 117: 22)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 117: 23)
          - May (Box-folder 117: 24)
      - Press releases
        - 1971
          - June (Box-folder 117: 25)
          - September (Box-folder 117: 26)
        - 1972 October (Box-folder 117: 27)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 117: 28)
      - Printed matter, undated (Box-folder 117: 29)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 117: 30)
        - 1972 October (Box-folder 117: 31)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 117: 32)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 117: 33)
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 117: 34)
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 117: 35)
        - 1972
          - February (Box-folder 117: 36)
          - September-October (Box-folder 117: 37-38)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 117: 39)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 117: 40)
      - Reports, 1969 June (Box-folder 117: 41)
      - Schedules
        - Undated (Box-folder 117: 42)
        - 1971 June-July (Box-folder 117: 43-44)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 117: 45)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 117: 46)
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 117: 47)
        - 1971
          - June (Box-folder 117: 48)
          - November (Box-folder 117: 49)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 117: 50)
        - 1973 November (Box-folder 117: 51)
      - Television news reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 117: 52)
        - 1972 March (Box-folder 117: 53)
    - Economy
      - Brochures, 1975 May (Box-folder 117: 54)
      - Correspondence
        - Undated (Box-folder 117: 55)
        - 1969 November (Box-folder 117: 56)
        - 1970
          - February (Box-folder 117: 57)
          - August-October (Box-folder 117: 58-60)
        - 1971
          - February (Box-folder 117: 61)
          - June (Box-folder 117: 62)
          - August-November (Box-folder 117: 63-66)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 117: 67)
          - March (Box-folder 117: 68)
          - December (Box-folder 117: 69)
        - 1973
          - January-March (Box-folder 117: 70-72)
          - December (Box-folder 117: 73)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 117: 74)
          - May-July (Box-folder 117: 75-77)
        - 1975
          - June (Box-folder 117: 78)
          - September (Box-folder 117: 79)
      - Executive orders
        - Undated (Box-folder 118: 1)
        - 1970
          - June (Box-folder 118: 2)
          - October (Box-folder 118: 3)
        - 1971
          - February (Box-folder 118: 4)
          - August (Box-folder 118: 5)
          - October-December (Box-folder 118: 6-8)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 118: 9)
          - March-April (Box-folder 118: 10-11)
          - June (Box-folder 118: 12)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 118: 13)
          - June-July (Box-folder 118: 14-15)
          - October (Box-folder 118: 16)
          - December (Box-folder 118: 17)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 118: 18)
          - May-June (Box-folder 118: 19-20)
          - October-November (Box-folder 118: 21-22)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 118: 23-24)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 118: 25)
        - 1969 January (Box-folder 118: 26)
        - 1970
          - February (Box-folder 118: 27)
          - April-May (Box-folder 118: 28-29)
          - August (Box-folder 118: 30)
        - 1971
          - General (Box-folder 118: 31)
          - January-May (Box-folder 118: 32-36)
          - October (Box-folder 118: 37)
          - December (Box-folder 118: 38)
        - 1972
          - General (Box-folder 118: 39)
          - June (Box-folder 118: 40)
          - August (Box-folder 118: 41)
        - 1973
          - General (Box-folder 118: 42)
          - January-April (Box-folder 118: 43-46)
          - June (Box-folder 118: 47)
          - July (Box-folder 119: 1)
            Includes booklet.
          - September (Box-folder 119: 2)
          - November-December (Box-folder 119: 3-4)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 119: 5-6)
          - May (Box-folder 119: 7)
          - July-August (Box-folder 119: 8-9)
          - November (Box-folder 119: 10)
        - 1975
          - February-April (Box-folder 119: 11-13)
          - July (Box-folder 119: 14)
      - Interviews
        - 1971
          - August (Box-folder 119: 15)
          - October-December (Box-folder 119: 16-18)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 119: 19)
          - July (Box-folder 119: 20)
          - November (Box-folder 119: 21)
        - 1973
          - January-March (Box-folder 119: 22-24)
          - July (Box-folder 119: 25)
        - 1974
          - May (Box-folder 119: 26)
          - July (Box-folder 119: 27)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 119: 28)
          - March (Box-folder 119: 29)
          - June (Box-folder 119: 30)
      - Meetings
        - Undated (Box-folder 119: 31)
        - 1970
          - February-March (Box-folder 119: 32-33)
          - August (Box-folder 119: 34)
          - November-December (Box-folder 119: 35-36)
        - 1971
          - January-July (Box-folder 119: 37-43)
          - September-October (Box-folder 119: 44-45)
          - December (Box-folder 119: 46)
        - 1972
          - January-March (Box-folder 119: 47-49)
          - June-October (Box-folder 119: 50-54)
            Includes clipping.
          - December (Box-folder 119: 55)
        - 1973
          - February-March (Box-folder 120: 1-2)
          - June (Box-folder 120: 3)
          - September (Box-folder 120: 4)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 120: 5-6)
          - April-November (Box-folder 120: 7-14)
        - 1975
          - January-February (Box-folder 120: 15-16)
          - April-June (Box-folder 120: 17-19)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 120: 20)
        - 1969
          - March (Box-folder 120: 21)
          - June (Box-folder 120: 22)
          - December (Box-folder 120: 23)
        - 1970
          - Undated (Box-folder 120: 24)
          - January-February (Box-folder 120: 25-26)
          - April-June (Box-folder 120: 27-29)
          - August-December (Box-folder 120: 30-34)
        - 1971
          - January-September (Box-folder 120: 35-43)
          - October-December (Box-folder 121: 1-3)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 121: 4)
          - March-December (Box-folder 121: 5-14)
        - 1973
          - January-October (Box-folder 121: 15-24)
          - December (Box-folder 121: 25)
        - 1974 (Box-folder 121: 26-37)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 121: 38)
          - April-June (Box-folder 121: 39-41)
      - Messages
        - Undated (Box-folder 122: 1)
        - 1969
          - July (Box-folder 122: 2)
          - October (Box-folder 122: 3)
        - 1970
          - General (draft) (Box-folder 122: 4)
          - February-April (Box-folder 122: 5-7)
        - 1971
          - February-April (Box-folder 122: 8-10)
          - June (Box-folder 122: 11)
          - December (Box-folder 122: 12)
        - 1972
          - May (Box-folder 122: 13)
          - July-August (Box-folder 122: 14-15)
        - 1973
          - January-April (Box-folder 122: 16-19)
          - September-October (Box-folder 122: 20-21)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 122: 22-23)
          - August (Box-folder 122: 24)
          - November (Box-folder 122: 25)
        - 1975 March-May (Box-folder 122: 26-28)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 122: 29)
      - Newsletters
        - Undated (Box-folder 122: 30)
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 122: 31)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 122: 32)
          - August (Box-folder 122: 33)
          - October (Box-folder 122: 34)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 122: 35)
        - 1974 November (Box-folder 122: 36)
      - News summaries
        - General (Box-folder 123: 1)
        - Undated (Box-folder 123: 2)
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 123: 3)
        - 1971
          - January-February (Box-folder 123: 4-5)
          - August (Box-folder 123: 6)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 123: 7)
          - August-December (Box-folder 123: 8-12)
        - 1973
          - January-March (Box-folder 123: 13-15)
          - June (Box-folder 123: 16)
          - September (Box-folder 123: 17)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 123: 18)
          - July (Box-folder 123: 19)
      - Pool reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 123: 20)
        - 1974 May-June (Box-folder 123: 21-22)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 123: 23)
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 123: 24)
        - 1971
          - January (Box-folder 123: 25)
          - March-December (Box-folder 123: 26-35)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 123: 36)
          - March-April (Box-folder 123: 37-38)
          - June-December (Box-folder 123: 39-45)
        - 1973
          - January-May (Box-folder 123: 46-50)
          - June-November (Box-folder 124: 1-6)
        - 1974 (Box-folder 124: 7-18)
        - 1975 January-July (Box-folder 124: 19-25)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 124: 26)
        - 1969
          - January (Box-folder 124: 27)
          - December (Box-folder 124: 28)
        - 1970
          - January (Box-folder 124: 29)
          - March (Box-folder 124: 30)
          - May-September (Box-folder 124: 31-35)
          - October (Box-folder 125: 1)
          - December (Box-folder 125: 2)
        - 1971 (Box-folder 125: 3-14)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 125: 15)
          - March-October (Box-folder 125: 16-23)
          - November-December (Box-folder 126: 1-2)
            Includes transcript.
        - 1973
          - January-October (Box-folder 126: 3-12)
          - December (Box-folder 126: 13)
        - 1974
          - January-March (Box-folder 126: 14-16)
          - May-July (Box-folder 126: 17-19)
          - October-November (Box-folder 126: 20-21)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 127: 1)
          - March-May (Box-folder 127: 2-4)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 127: 5)
        - 1969 February (Box-folder 127: 6)
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 127: 7)
        - 1971
          - January-February (Box-folder 127: 8-9)
          - April (Box-folder 127: 10)
          - August-October (Box-folder 127: 11-13)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 127: 14)
          - April (Box-folder 127: 15)
          - June-August (Box-folder 127: 16-18)
          - December (Box-folder 127: 19)
        - 1973
          - January-April (Box-folder 127: 20-23)
          - June (Box-folder 127: 24)
          - December (Box-folder 127: 25)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 127: 26-27)
          - July (Box-folder 127: 28)
          - September-October (Box-folder 127: 29-30)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 127: 31)
      - Printed matter
        - General, 1969 (Box-folder 127: 32)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 127: 33)
        - 1973 July (Box-folder 127: 34)
        - 1974 November (Box-folder 127: 35)
      - Proclamations, 1971 August (Box-folder 127: 36)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 127: 37)
        - 1969 November-December (Box-folder 127: 38-39)
        - 1970
          - January (Box-folder 127: 40)
          - April-August (Box-folder 127: 41-45)
          - December (Box-folder 127: 46)
        - 1971
          - January-June (Box-folder 127: 47-52)
          - August-December (Box-folder 127: 53-57)
        - 1972
          - January-February (Box-folder 127: 58-59)
          - March-June (Box-folder 128: 1-4)
          - September-October (Box-folder 128: 5-6)
        - 1973
          - General (Box-folder 128: 7)
          - January-March (Box-folder 128: 8-10)
          - May-July (Box-folder 128: 11-13)
          - September (Box-folder 128: 14)
          - November (Box-folder 128: 15)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 128: 16)
          - April-July (Box-folder 128: 17-20)
          - September-October (Box-folder 128: 21-22)
          - December (Box-folder 128: 23)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 128: 24)
          - March-July (Box-folder 128: 25-29)
      - Reports
        - 1970
          - February (Box-folder 128: 30)
          - August (Box-folder 128: 31)
          - December (Box-folder 128: 32)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 128: 33)
          - October (Box-folder 128: 34)
          - December (Box-folder 129: 1)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 129: 2)
          - August (Box-folder 129: 3)
        - 1973
          - January-February (Box-folder 129: 4-5)
          - April (Box-folder 129: 6)
          - June (Box-folder 129: 7)
        - 1974
          - May (Box-folder 129: 8)
          - September (Box-folder 129: 9)
      - Schedules
        - Undated (Box-folder 129: 10)
        - 1970
          - July (Box-folder 129: 11)
          - December (Box-folder 129: 12)
        - 1971
          - January (Box-folder 129: 13)
          - May (Box-folder 129: 14)
          - October (Box-folder 129: 15)
        - 1973
          - January-March (Box-folder 129: 16-18)
          - June-July (Box-folder 129: 19-20)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 129: 21)
          - May (Box-folder 129: 22)
          - September (Box-folder 129: 23)
          - November (Box-folder 129: 24)
        - 1975 February (Box-folder 129: 25)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 129: 26)
        - 1969
          - April-May (Box-folder 129: 27-28)
          - December (Box-folder 129: 29)
        - 1970
          - April-August (Box-folder 129: 30-34)
          - October (Box-folder 129: 35)
          - December (Box-folder 129: 36)
        - 1971
          - General (draft) (Box-folder 129: 37)
          - March (Box-folder 129: 38)
          - May (Box-folder 129: 39)
          - August-October (Box-folder 129: 40-42)
          - November-December (Box-folder 130: 1-2)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 130: 3)
          - March-April (Box-folder 130: 4-5)
          - June-September (Box-folder 130: 6-9)
          - December (Box-folder 130: 10)
        - 1973
          - January-July (Box-folder 130: 11-17)
          - September (Box-folder 130: 18)
          - November-December (Box-folder 130: 19-20)
        - 1974
          - March-June (Box-folder 130: 21-24)
          - August (Box-folder 130: 25)
          - December (Box-folder 130: 26)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 130: 27)
          - March-April (Box-folder 130: 28-29)
          - June (Box-folder 130: 30)
      - Telegrams
        - 1970 February (Box-folder 130: 31)
        - 1971
          - January (Box-folder 130: 32)
          - November (Box-folder 130: 33)
      - Television news reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 130: 34)
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 130: 35)
        - 1971 August-December (Box-folder 130: 36-40)
        - 1972
          - January-March (Box-folder 130: 41-43)
          - June (Box-folder 130: 44)
        - 1973
          - January-March (Box-folder 130: 45-47)
          - June-July (Box-folder 130: 48-49)
          - December (Box-folder 130: 50)
        - 1974
          - April-May (Box-folder 130: 51-52)
          - July (Box-folder 130: 53)
          - November (Box-folder 130: 54)
    - Education
      - Correspondence
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 131: 1)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 131: 2)
      - Executive orders, 1974 January (Box-folder 131: 3)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 131: 4)
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 131: 5)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 131: 6)
      - Meetings
        - General (Box-folder 131: 7)
        - 1970
          - July (Box-folder 131: 8)
          - November (Box-folder 131: 9)
        - 1971
          - February-March (Box-folder 131: 10-11)
          - May (Box-folder 131: 12)
          - September (Box-folder 131: 13)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 131: 14)
          - September (Box-folder 131: 15)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 131: 16)
        - 1975 February (Box-folder 131: 17)
      - Memoranda
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 131: 18)
        - 1971
          - February-March (Box-folder 131: 19-20)
          - May (Box-folder 131: 21)
          - September (Box-folder 131: 22)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 131: 23)
          - September-October (Box-folder 131: 24-25)
        - 1974
          - March (Box-folder 131: 26)
          - August (Box-folder 131: 27)
      - Messages
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 131: 28)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 131: 29)
        - 1972 August (Box-folder 131: 30)
        - 1973 July (Box-folder 131: 31)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 131: 32)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 131: 33-34)
      - Press briefings
        - 1971 April-June (Box-folder 131: 35-37)
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 131: 38)
      - Press conferences
        - 1969 February (Box-folder 131: 39)
        - 1970
          - March-April (Box-folder 131: 40-41)
          - June-July (Box-folder 131: 42-43)
        - 1971
          - February (Box-folder 131: 44)
          - September (Box-folder 131: 45)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 131: 46)
          - June (Box-folder 131: 47)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 131: 48)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 131: 49)
      - Press releases
        - 1970